No?
Perfume?
Koichan, lift your head.
Is it a hot spring?
I don't know.
But it's only available at the store.
Oh, I'm here!
It's so bright!
Hello!
Why don't you go buy some Cagrars?
You can buy it... now...
I wonder if there are ramen noodles...
I'm going to eat ramen noodles!
I'm so hungry
It's so bright
Miffy!
Oh no, no, no, no, no
Elegant
I'm going for a walk with my kindergartener today
I'm going for a walk with kindergartners
With kindergartners
Yes
A walk
What?
Where do you want to go? Rina-chan
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to the main store.
The main store is kind of a high quality place, isn't it?
It's close.
What's wrong, Haru?
I found an amusement park.
You said we should go.
The main store is kind of high class, isn't it?
It's close. It's close.
That's high quality land.
Two kilometers?
Two kilometers.
You don't walk 2 kilometers.
Two kilometers?
Haru.
You said you wanted to go.
Okay, that's enough.
Then I want to go to the amusement park.
Two kilometers is too much.
I'll do my best
Like an automatic grasshopper
It's your last day.
To push that thing.
Again.
Mada Mada
celebratory New Year's wind
Yes, it is.
Hello.
Looks delicious.
It's a nice atmosphere.
It's so green and beautiful.
It's nice.
I want to eat something like this.
I want some!
I want to eat Mitarashi dango in a place like this.
You like them?
I think I'd like that.
Really?
Yeah.
Left, Shan!
This one's green.
It's really beautiful.
It's full of air. The air is stuffy.
They're going to an amusement park.
Amusement park?
They have an amusement park! Isn't it great?
Is it really there?
I want to play.
I want to play!
Snazai Stenman's
Lau
Irimikuman
I knew we have light hair color.
Oh, but it's okay.
Are you sure they're gone?
He's really gone, isn't he?
Yes!
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
Yay!
Calm down.
I'm really... I'm really...
I really am.
I know. I know.
Look, look, look.
It flew, it flew, it flew, it flew.
Who flew?
It was a limo mamachuko.
Let's do it together.
Sora gave it to me.
Bon appétit!
It's still rice cakes.
The end.
Wait a minute.
What's that?
Mochi with red bean paste.
Delicious.
Ma-chan.
Yoo-hoo! Yoo-hoo!
YouTube is on the side. YouTube is horizontal.
Not YouTube.
That's it, isn't it? It's Kayu-chan's treasure.
I don't have any treasure.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
Thank you for watching.
I'm trying to be fast.
I'll get your feet.
Here you go. Cheese.
Tail too fast.
I've touched everything I can touch
Yu is for better eyes.
My eyes, my head, to lose weight
I touched her body too
I touched her body, and her legs
I want to be smart
I've touched my head
It's so much fun when everyone comes to the amusement park.
Now, let's go.
We want to go to the amusement park now.
We come to the amusement park.
We want to go to the amusement park.
There we go.
There's a meaning to the bridge, and it means past, present, and future.
What?
There's a meaning to the bridge, and there's a meaning to the past, present, and future.
When you walk before the eternal future...
But there, too... then the future...
By the way, you shouldn't cut your buttocks off either.
Ah! Aah! Aah!
Don't peel off!
I knew it!
I didn't peel it! It's not cut and peeled!
It's not cropped here.
No, it's not!
How can it not be cropped?
It's on this side!
It came out this side!
We're at the beginning.
I'm sure!
Mommy, hold my hand.
Hey, Moe-chan!
This is now.
How's the present? Is it current?
I'm too hungry.
What? You're hungry?
You're lying.
We're all hungry.
I'm so hungry.
I had some umegae mochi at home, but I really wanted to eat some.
I'm losing weight at home, so I can't eat it. I'd like to eat it again when I visit Fukuoka.
I see.
My body...
What's wrong with you? This is the future.
They want to take pictures here?
How do you like the future?
Slope.
Is it different? It's the future.
Should we just stop here?
Yes.
Something's wrong with my eyes.
It's painful.
Congratulations.
I finally went inside.
Yay.
It's like some kind of flappy cheese.
Like moon ice.
Eat it quickly.
tener tener
entar this kes ASA
ah ah ah ah
ederim
I have a guy who pushes me back.
I'm not pushing you.
I'm trying to protect you.
I'm just trying to protect you.
Don't swim.
I'm not swimming.
Hey, beautiful lady!
Beautiful lady!
I'm trying so hard to get you...
Oh, is it gone?
It's a little broken. I have to fix it.
That's great.
How do you like it?
It's beautiful.
I can hear the drums.
Oh, my God.
Beautiful, very beautiful.
Miyuki's is beautiful.
Eh? You say this?
I'm kidding!
Huh?
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you for watching.
Make-Alive.
Makeray, stop.
Thank you for watching
Is this a video?
Even in the video, it's blurry.
Why is it blurry?
It's blurry!
You're the only one who looks good in the video!
It's so beautiful, but... It's so beautiful, but I knew it.
Cinnabatik.
Oh, no, no, it's an umbrella.
I want to do a fortune.
Let's do it together.
I absolutely love it.
It's fun!
I want to draw a picture too.
I want to draw fortunes!
Oh, you don't want to draw, you want to draw.
You draw your own fortune?
That's unusual.
You're a rare type.
Here.
Our eyes met.
Let's open it together.
It's not open yet, guys.
It's not open.
It's open.
Come on, let's do it.
Okay, we're open.
Okay, let's get it right here.
I'm nervous.
Ready?
Masayoshi!
Shokichi!
It's Shokichi!
I wonder if there are many Shokichi.
Look how cute it is!
Daikichi.
It was “Daikichi”.
Number 24.
It's the same...
Number 25.
I was with Sora. I was with Sora.
Wow!
Look at all of them!
It's so heavy!
It's heavy!
I'll fix it.
One at a time, on camera, please.
One at a time, please.
That's great!
Good luck, number 24.
The goal will be achieved in a big way.
I'll do my best.
Your desire will be fulfilled.
I will cherish my sincerity
I will do my best to cherish my sincerity
Yu's result is the same as Sora's
The same as Sora's
It was “Shokichi
I'm afraid I'm coming too
It looks like I won't be able to fulfill my wish.
It's the luck of change.
It's the luck of change in a good way.
By changing, our luck will improve.
I'll do my best.
I'm with Yu.
Exactly the same.
We had the same number, 12.
Weather
I want to live alone
It's not a slip, but...
I'll be careful with the directions.
Well...
I wonder what it means...
I'm the girl who seems to eat raw, but I have a solid fortune... and I'm laying the foundations, so I'll do my best next time
Next... it's “big luck”... and you'll have the good fortune of co-starring.
I'll be able to do what I want, wait for the right person, get in early, have a pleasant trip, and have everything resolved in my favor.
I'm a student for the entrance examination I'm so happy! I'm a student. I'm so happy!
Yes, what's that? Shokichi, 20 percent.
I'm in commerce, right? Commerce is a job, right?
I'll be patient... and do my best this year.
Thank you very much
I like to travel, but I'm told that it's better to travel far away from home, so I'm going to go on a trip that I can't softly take.
So I'm going on a trip that I can't soften up.
Designer cks, even if you go to the big headache 1617 wow!
Eassing сама
me widgets pae history
How's it going?
I don't know.
I don't feel bad.
You just did that twice in a row.
It says here that hard work always pays off.
Oh, really?
If you say it twice...
Earlier, Mikuri...
You told me to be sincere.
I still have sincerity.
I do feel like I have sincerity.
Let's take our toys
A word from each of you.
I said a word.
Me too, Lurin.
Oh, I see.
One more thing.
How are you, Rina?
How are you?
I need your energy.
Rina-chan.
Rina-chan
Rina-chan!
That's a tiny ball!
Here you go.
What's up?
A silicone snake? Snakes in silicon?
A silicon snake?
What?
I can't win.
A silicone snake?
You like silicone snakes?
I could win.
It's moving, it's moving, it's moving.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
Oh, it's an E series, isn't it?
I don't know why it's gone.
house lizard
I saw it!
That's where they cut off the tail.
Different colors...
They cut off so many tails!
Now, look at this.
What's going on?
It's amazing!
It stopped.
Yes, sir.
Wow, Ri-chan, can you touch it?
Don't you want to go like this?
Like this.
But it's like this, right?
The normal way.
But I'm just...
I'm helping you.
You're right.
Oh, you mean you're going like this?
I can't. Not without you.
I touched it in elementary school, but I'm kind of out of practice now.
I'm kind of blank. I'm kind of blank.
Wasn't it popular in elementary school or something?
It was.
Some people do.
But, but yeah. But, but yeah.
Don't you know that much?
Can't you just touch it?
Oh, but something...
Oh, I haven't noticed.
What?
That looks scary.
I'm sorry. You scared me.
Oh, my God.
I'm worried about you being in there.
Let's go to a meeting like that at the most.
Cheese and cheese.
Hello.
Thank you for watching.
I don't know.
I don't know. It's like a match.
Koharu, what are you doing?
Koharu, I'm here.
I can't do this.
I can't do it.
She's mad.
I won't lose my temper.
She'll just take her stuff and go.
You're too strong.
You're too strong!
Thank you very much.
These are popsicles!
I bought it with Momo and Momo.
I bought some Momo Momo, too.
This is tangerine.
Tangerine flavor?
It's delicious.
It's cute. What is it?
This one tastes like peaches.
But I don't know.
It's cute.
Peach peach is a Kawny flavor.
Like blueberry, like tree nuts. Like blueberries, like tree nuts.
Delicious.
I don't know, but I've eaten a lot of them.
Delicious
Delicious!
Let's eat it.
It's good!
It's the best!
And the hot bisphyscream.
Bon appétit.
Yummy?
It's so good!
Sora.
No, I just took it.
A video? Yes, for YouTube.
For YouTube.
You all bought something, didn't you?
Shumai and...
Steamed meat buns? I got a steamed bun.
It's so cute!
Looks delicious!
Yoo, you too!
Yoo bought shao mai too!
Shumai shumai!
Let's eat!
Steamed meat buns!
Wow, steamed buns!
Looks delicious!
I'll eat it!
Bon appétit!
I ate a popsicle!
Yes, Bon appétit.
Here you go.
How about a Mental Seamonik? Here you go.
Hot!
Delicious!
Not a bit dry. There is no para.
All the mental seamonics.
Amazing!!!
I can't show you.
Delicious!
I'll take half a Dorito.
I'm so happy.
It's for you, bear. Have a nice drink.
It's so rich. Very tasty.
Oh, it's not banana. Does it taste like mango?
It tastes like mango. It's so good. Okay, with a straw.
It's so easy. Bear, it's coming down.
It's delicious.
It's so rich, isn't it? And it's...
It's so delicious.
This bear.
Is it falling?
I don't know. I can't see it.
I can't see it either.
It's cute.
It's delicious.
That's all for now.
I'll take you back.
Poor thing.
It's plum soft.
Here you go.
But I don't think it smells very good.
You don't smell it?
Bon appétit.
Ume.
Ume?
Very tasty.
Very tasty?
Hey...
It's delicious.
Really? Really?
It doesn't look like much in terms of color.
Eat it.
It's delicious.
May I?
Yeah, eat it.
It doesn't look like a top at all, but it's really good.
It's so good!
It's delicious!
Isn't it good?
Jan, kakuni!
What's that?
Kakuni Manjuu.
Ta-da!
Looks delicious!
Looks delicious, I'll eat it. But it's too chewy.
You can't eat it, Lorin!
Yeah, blubbl, blubbl, blubbl, so good!
It's soft. It's so soft. It's so soft and pulled.
Did you drop it?
I didn't drop it.
Just make sure you're holding it.
Mango juice is so good.
It's delicious.
Oh, my God.
It looks like a hamburger.
Yeah, it's got the right shape.
He said he wouldn't give it to you.
For Mr. Hart.
Bon appétit!
It's so rich!
It's rich, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Isn't it soft?
Warm.
Tasty?Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
Rina's scared of pigeons.
Hey, I am.
Is it good?
Stewed cubes, mango jus and stewed cubes in a bun.
Stewed cubes, mango jus and stewed cubes in a bun?
Yeah, a bun.
Yay.
What did you buy?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Mentaiko steamed buns.
Wow, I'll eat it!
You're so cute!
It's so cute!
It's a little miniature and cute!
Look at that!
It really is!
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
Thank you for watching.
Looks hot.
No, it's good.
Delicious?
The meat, the meat of a regular bun, and the cod roe go well together.
How is it?
The cheese is a little bit sweet.
A little spicy.
It's good.
It's dazzling.
Yummy?
I'll have some cod roe.
A steamed bun.
Next, Harina will eat it.
Come on, Ella.
Here, here.
Like this.
You need an insert.I need an insert.
I'll take it.
I'll take a bite.
Yum!
It's warm!
Hey, I gotta go!
Delicious! The cod roe is not too strong.
Not too much.
Yes, yes, yes.
And the bun skin is a little sweet, right?
Yes, sweet!
The mentaiko is spicy, so it's just right.
Harmony?
How is it? Good?
Mazaria Harmony.
I'm gonna give this an overnighter.
Overnight flush.
It's good.
What do you want it for?
Delicious!
You haven't had it yet?
I thought you might want some.
Bon appétit.
I can't open my eyes.
I don't remember it being like this.
Do people open their eyes?
I'm not blind yet.
I don't have eyes!
I got the rice cakes!
Bon appétit!
Oh, just like that?
No, it's not.
Dumpy, isn't it?
The sticky chicken is delicious!
Bon appétit!
It's so big, I want to take it home.
Delicious!
Delicious!Delicious
Stamps are delicious
It's not quite the same as this
It's a little bit sticky.
What's this?
What do you call it? With a reddish paste?
All I could get was glue.
I'm sorry.
It's good.
I'm not satisfied.
I'm not happy.
Bye bye.
Welcome.
What's with the natural light?
Eh, flat bangs.
It's like natural light.
Flattened bangs
Unfinished light
Oh no!
Maru-chan really likes me, doesn't she?
Maru-chan's on board.
Everyone, please do it again.
Don't stop the camera.
Excuse me.
Can you just avoid the comments?
Awkward?
Awkward.
Look, there's another camera over there.
I'm filming.
It was fun. We all had fun.
We kind of split it between Ryu and Aus.
We went to each other's places, but we got together at the end.
Everyone was eating their favorite food.
They're eating.
I love it so much!